(Raj:)Now, here are some secret facts
about each of you,
(Raj:)including whether
you are the murderer.
(Raj:)Throughout the game, feel free
(Raj:)to ask each other questions
to uncover clues.
(Penny:)Got it.
(Penny:)Hey, who's the murderer?
(Raj:)Any question but that.
(Penny:)Sorry.
(Penny:)Hey, who's not the murderer?
(Stuart:)Bernadette, can you not stand
so close to me?
(Bernadette:)What do you care? You're dead.
(Stuart:)Suit yourself.
But I can kind of see up your skirt.
(Sheldon:)Thank you for my bobble head.
(Howard:)Thank you for not making fun
of me during my speech.
(Sheldon:)It wasn't easy. Was it Buzz?
(Howard:)We can't show up to
your mom's empty-handed.
(Howard:)We should bring something.
(Sheldon:)I already am.
I'm bringing the gift of knowledge.